Do you have a message for the kids in Palestine?
Free free!
Palestine!
My love!
A message for the children in Palestine?
Yes.
Be careful.
That is amazing.
Did you know that you're a hero for being here?
Did you know that?
I didn't know.
Well, I'm telling you now.
There's people that are way older than you that are scared to be here.
I'm very proud of you.
Have a nice day my love.
Thank you.
Why are you marching?
I'm going to stop killing Gaza.
Can I hear you say free free?
Free free!
Free!
Palestine!
Free free!
Do you have a message for the kids in Palestine?
Yeah.
What do you want to say?
Bubbles?
What's that?
Oh, we love you!
Is that what you said?
My love!
Do you think this is a hate march?
No.
No, it's not, is it?
Yeah.
Can you say, um, Suella Braverman, shame on you?
Suella Braverman, shame on you.